One dream, one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marks maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
Oh!
Oh, a secret mission! Okay.
So all we need is a plan.
I have a proposal.
In two weeks' time, we
will head to Onigashima.
It's an island home to Kaido and
the base of the Beast Pirates.
An island? What?
You're telling me it's
not on the mainland,
so we have to travel by sea to get to it?
Indeed.
Fortuitously, it's not far.
In fact, it's nearly visible from
the land of Wano's shoreline.
We will still require a ship,
though not a very large one.
Cool.
We'll figure out all those
little details at a later date.
When do you need all of us ready?
We have a day in mind.
The best time would be the
night of the Fire Festival.
It's a grand celebration for
the people of the capital.
Simply put, Kaido himself
is believed to be a deity.
They think he protects the land,
so Orochi will lead the shogun's
procession to pay tribute that day.
But that is merely a facade.
What really takes place is a pretentious
banquet for magistrates and beast pirates.
A fine target.
Makes a lot of sense.
So we wait till they get wasted.
Use that to our advantage
and knock those jerks
around And then chop the
heads off their leaders
Hey!
I gotta give you a quick warning though,
Okiku You'll fall in love after seeing
me kick ass You hear that, sword pervert?
Please calm yourself, Sir Sanji.
Do not be mistaken.
I am a perfectly happy married fellow.
Okiku is but a comrade of mine.
I promise you that there is
no deeper relationship here.
Speaking of which, your wife as well?
Huh?
You saw Otsuru?
Indeed
Incognito.
Splendid.
Good to know she's doing well.
But I cannot be selfish
and go see her yet.
Not until our work is done.
Master Keen.
Stop it!
You're a married man!
You can't hog all the ladies!
Oh, Kiku, I'm more
deserving of your attention.
Knock it off, you.
Hey, Sanji, did you know
Kiku's super strong? Uh-uh.
Beautiful and a strong warrior?
You're perfect.
Now then, I have designed a symbol
to help with getting the word out:
two birds of flame to represent time,
a habu viper to indicate location,
and a reverse crescent moon
which signifies rebellion,
twilight—the second hour of
the bird at fire festival.
It shall take place in Habu Port.
port If that doesn't make sense, it refers
to the period between 5.30 and 6.00 p .m.
on your foreign clocks.
Don't fret.
This is normal in Wano.
They'll understand.
We will venture out, distributing
flyers to anyone bearing the mark,
a moon etched on the left ankle.
That is the symbol of insurrection.
They are our allies.
There is only one problem.
We don't know how many are out there.
But we've taken steps
to maximize our reach.
We have comrades spread about
the country getting the word out.
Based at the capital, both Sir Zorojuro
and Sir Usohachi are aiding us.
Uh, sorry to say, but I
don't think Zoro's helping.
That aside, Sir Furnosuke has disguised
himself as a carpenter's apprentice.
Having located the craftsman
who designed Kaido's mansion,
we hope to obtain those blueprints.
They will be essential.
Getting lost is not an option.
As for Madam Orobi, she's infiltrated
the walls of Orochi's palace.
Vital to our plan, she's keeping tabs on
the Shogun's forces while entertaining him.
Rumor has it she's quite popular.
Rocking a geisha get up my heart!
Now we're together, I wish to
delegate roles to you latecomers.
Sir Brook, your ability will be essential
in helping procure food from the capital.
It will?
I mean, I guess.
Your weather control is like ninjutsu,
so you'll be a kunoichi, Madam Nami.
A female ninja?
A kunoichi! Oh, Nami!
I take that.
You'll be adorable.
Sir Sanji's cooking will
attract attention and
also assist us in recruiting
others for our quest.
Following?
Of course I'll do it.
And what about me?
You shall be paired up with Sir Chopper.
I'd like for you two, along with
Kiku, to join Dogstorm's side.
Cannon, can I dress like a ninja too?
Don't see why not?
Now that you know your missions, I shall
provide clothes suited for each of you.
Please kindly take these leaves
and place them upon your heads.
Are you ready?
Here goes.
Prepare yourselves!
Garb-garb-jutsu manifest!
And boom!
Nami, wow!
Take a look at you!
Yeah! Ninja!
You may go about your missions,
since you are in the correct attire.
Hold up, Kin'emon.
This isn't a real ninja outfit.
On the contrary.
That's the ideal look!
I think you're lying to my face!
Moving on, allow me to summon
a guide, a real Kunoichi.
Come out!
I wonder if she's alive!
Can't wait to meet her! Shinobu!
I heed your call.
I knew my outfit was off!
What a joke!
You bastard!
This is really bad! He's shaking!
I think he's in shock!
Kin'emon, you want to explain this to me?
The world of Kunoichi is divided in two.
Either sexy or frumpy.
If I can pull this up, I'll deal.
Looking good, Brooke.
What are you supposed to be?
Well, I assumed I was a man
with panties on his head.
But come to think of
it, now I'm not so sure.
That's funny.
How nice to be so young
and full of spirit.
You all may call me Shinobu.
In the past, I was like a
little sister to Master King.
Alas, that was long ago.
I specialize in seduction jutsu.
Pleasure to meet you.
If it weren't for Nami's outfit,
I'd be a broken man right now.
Stay with me!
Oh, I do understand, young man.
Nothing is more deadly
than a mature woman.
All right!
We shall split up until our
forces are all gathered.
Take note of three samurai in
particular we hope to recruit.
Finding them will be a tremendous help.
They are Kawamatsu,
Ashida Doji, and Denjiro.
Much like your present company,
they too once served Lord Odin.
It's time.
Best of luck with your objectives.
We are closing in on our wretched targets.
The Shogun Orochi and Kaido 2.
The fire festivals in two weeks.
That's the execution date.
We'll storm Kaido's base on Onigashima and
return this nation to its former glory!
Oh, my God.
Well, hello.
Take it all.
You can't keep the good stuff to yourself.
You got to share.
Give it back.
Luffy Toto brought us that.
We may never see riches like
this again. I don't care.
Oh, Mama.
Huh?
They've got sake, too.
This is fancy.
Awful greedy.
How could you?
My grandson is so hungry.
Shut your trap!
Just die already!
Huh?
Move!
Somebody's got a fat head.
Who the hell would pull
off a heist like this?
Acting like some hero and
giving food to the poor?
They're selling you
hope when there is none.
You get your food, then
you lose it just as fast.
Slipping through your fingers
like it was just a dream.
There's no samurai here who will
stand up for the downtrodden.
They all lost their spines.
There's no one left to lead them either.
No men with honor or
conviction or an ounce of guts.
There's no one left to
keep this ship on course.
The land of Wano is finished.
You all know it.
Hear that, you old hag?
You're holding on to
life for no damn reason.
All you're gonna see is more
suffering and more senseless cruelty!
Should I put you out of your misery?
Please run! Grandma!
I believe in Lady Odoki's
words, and I always will.
Ha!
She's long dead.
The nine samurai will return to this land,
and Lord Odin's dream will
surely be fulfilled. Yeah? How?
Who could take Odin's place?
Who could lead their revolt?
Shitenmaru!
Sir, this is bad! No!
No!
So, we meet at last.
The head of the Thieves Brigade. Whoa!
That thing's a monster!
A pirate named Straw Hat Luffy came
around here recently. Seen anything?
If I tell you I don't know him,
will you turn around and leave?
Because I doubt that.
Watch your tongue, thief.
You're lucky,
Kaido wants you as part
of his crew because if it
was up to me I would have
stomped you out long ago,
so if you think I owed you even an
ounce of respect, you're mistaken.
All right, if you hate me so much!
But I've only got one answer for you!
Real quick, Kin'emon,
I understand your strategy so far but
there's one thing I'm still confused about.
Odin brought down Ashura
Doji 20 years ago.
All right, but you also said he's
the one samurai we need to find.
He fought Odin but he's loyal to him.
A fair question to ask, I'd say.
It's quite simple.
Ashida Doji was defeated,
then mended his ways.
He pledged loyalty to Lord
Odin when he saw his worth.
But now...
It seems that he's doing
wicked deeds once more.
Shutenmaru, he's called.
He's the leader of the
Atamayama Thieves Brigade.
I swear I've heard that name.
I got a question.
Is he really strong?
Indeed.
Have no doubt.
In fact, he may be the
strongest samurai of all.
I'm ready.
Hey, shit!
Samurai aren't so weak.
Master Jack!
If it's your way.
Back away!
Master Jack is letting loose!
This is going to get ugly!
We're all doomed, aren't we?
No!
Ever since he died, I've
lost any reason to fight.
I've long since been ready to follow him.
However...
Getting killed by an underling
like you is not the answer!
Cut the crap!
I should have died
together with living
is suffering I'm so sick of it all
Ahhhh! Yeah!
Ahhhh!
Master Jack!
The sky! Look up!
Oh boy!
He came in person.
What could kind of be plotting?
Those clouds came out of
nowhere—guess it's gonna rain!
It's him!
Hey, Straw Hat, get over here!
here
I'm coming. What's up?
What the hell?
Lord Momonosuke! What?
Lord Momonosuke has changed.
He's a dragon?
I will explain the details
later, but this is no illusion.
His body can change forms.
Of all cursed things, the
poor boy has become a dragon!
This is bad.
Really bad.
Run! Run away!
What does he want?
Why now?
Hey, Jack.
Yes, sir.
Find those punks and bring them here.
Step on it or else.
Whoa!
What is that?
This couldn't get any worse.
That dragon...
is Kaido.
So that's him.
Kaido.
Wait, Kaido was a dragon?
Yes.
This is the opponent that we face.
A brutal warrior.
Who can transform into a beast.
Is he going in to Okapore?
I wonder, what could have brought
him to Kuma all of a sudden?
Sorry, Kin'emon.
We were identified by them.
Me, Straw Hat, and Zoro as well. You what?
But they only know that
we're here in Wano.
They don't know about the plan.
Is that supposed to be reassuring?
How'd you screw this up so bad?
You Straw Hats can't stick
to a plan to save your lives.
I don't have to take that from you.
It was Luffy's fault, wasn't it?
I'm sorry, Law. Again.
So given the timing, Kaido's probably
looking for me and Straw Hats.
The Beast Pirates have an
overwhelming presence here thanks to
two key resources they put all
their strength into producing.
First, there are the weapons that Kaido
is forcing the citizens to manufacture.
Second, there are the smiles
Kaido uses to fortify his troops.
These are the artificial devil
fruits made by Caesar and Doflamingo.
But, as you know, we cut
that off at the source.
After capturing Caesar and
destroying his lab on Punk Hazard,
any further smile
development was shut down.
after that we destroyed doflamingo's
factory and dress rosa this
shut down production and trade
distribution of smile in no time now
kaido's business partner is not
only dethroned but locked in prison
so in the simplest terms possible
we picked a fight with kaido
The Samurai aren't even on his radar.
He's just after me and Straw Hat.
Hey! Luffy!
Where are you going? Sir Luffy!
Stay here! Let me go!
They know about the two of us,
but they don't know that the
rest of our crews are here.
You need to stay out of
sight to keep that a secret.
Otherwise, they'll hunt us down.
This is obviously bad, but
let's work with what we've got.
Hawkins doesn't know much.
Continue with your plan.
Understand?
All right, but what about you two?
I wish I could let things be,
but Straw Hat's already gotten involved
with the people of this country.
If he can't control his
emotions, our plan will fail!
them.
We need the entire alliance with us.
That is the only way we can succeed.
I can
pull this together somehow.
Now, room.
In the meantime, stay out of sight.
It shambles.
Be careful!
Damn it, Luffy.
We weren't apart that
long. What did you do?
Thieves Brigade, retreat to the forest!
We don't want to get in a tussle with him!
I've heard many a tale, you know,
of the mighty brigandous underlings
living deep in the mountains of Khuri.
You may have changed your
name, but I remember you.
That's all in the past, though, right?
Just bow down to me, buddy.
I'd be happy to wipe the
slate clean between us.
Whoa, that stinks!
Kaido, don't tell me you're drunk!
Hmm?
What do you mean, Big Dummy?
Of course not.
He's super drunk!
What's it gonna be, Shetemura?
We can't run!
I'll have to create an opening!
I'm trying to stop the bleeding!
Please don't move, sir!
Yeah, but Commander Kaido is wasted.
There's no telling how
much damage he might do.
You're saying we gotta get
out of here or we're all dead?
That's a possibility, yeah.
I'm worried about the
people of Okamori Tower.
We need them to work in the factories.
It's fine if Kaido
wants to set an example,
but he can't just wreak
havoc all over Kuri.
He's gonna wipe out his own men.
You didn't think to share
that important detail with me?
Really?
Forgive me, Master Keen.
You return to Odin's palace.
Allow me to rescue Saru. Please.
I'm responsible as well.
Really, woman?
You should have taken another
husband to protect you.
Twenty long years.
You waited all this time for my return?
Saru, I shall make you wait no longer.
Damn, it's still a long way.
Right behind you, Straw Hats.
Hey, Traffy, you think the
people of Okoborre Town are okay?
They'd be a hell of a lot better if
some pirate didn't decide to play hero.
Mind your own business next time.
But it's us Kaido wants, not them, right?
It's gotta be.
Supreme Commander, sir!
Is it he?
One of the headliners?
Commander, I assume that you're searching
for Straw Hat Luffy and Trafalgar Law.
I have found them.
They're tucked away in
the ruins of Odin Castle.
Baton Kasseler.
Hawkers...
Is that true?
They've been hiding in those ruins
under our noses and we didn't know!
It's a lie.
I said it is a means of redirecting
his rampage. For a time.
However, this should work to our favor.
there is an old legend
attached to that castle
and because of it people
are claiming that they've
seen an eerie light there
they still believe that
that the kozuki samurai
will come back for revenge
from beyond the grave just
in time for the anniversary
huh indeed which i'm
certain has become a great
cause of stress for the
shogun so destroying that
castle would kill two
birds with with one stone.
Old Odin castle, huh?
That brings back memories.
It's a fine hiding place indeed.
But not anymore.
You're thinking punks can get
away with what you've done.
Taking my smile fruits away didn't stop.
You awoke by wrath.
What the hell, why is he
going toward the castle?
Hey, guys.
Oh, is it just me or is
he coming straight for us?
I think you're right.
But how did he notice
I was from so far away?
Oh, no.
Maybe he's just making a circle.
No.
He knows.
Run! Hurry!
Why is he headed straight for the castle?
It can't be.
Oh, no! Not that!
Run for it!
Shut up!
Last breath!
Captain, help!
Oh, my God.
Kaido!